{
    "id": "d6bfd34398ab41318e0bb619caa6481b",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. from the heat.",
            "description": "To faint is to lose consciousness.",
            "answers": [
                "feinted",
                "fainted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d80c296aa9d4f8488ed116b68e05cd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only a …………………….. sound came over the radio.",
            "description": "Faint can also mean feeble.",
            "answers": [
                "feint",
                "faint"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52fb48de43e6433987ca9cf7a4dfb057"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dogs made a few ………………………… at each other and then backed off without fighting",
            "description": "A feint is a feigned attack. ",
            "answers": [
                "faints",
                "feints"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fab5b47f1720480699fc7132d300cee9"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… countries can survive without trade.",
            "description": "Use few with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little",
                "Less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9a31f0abd2c40ed85118db69ce785a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t give me any more cookies – I still have ………………………..",
            "description": "A few means a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f4323cabb8045ccabd288b74421ef3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A good speaker does not ………………………. for words.",
            "description": "To flounder is to struggle clumsily.",
            "answers": [
                "founder",
                "flounder"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcaf9c5ec5414a02bb91bb99f5116175"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… the lamp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lit",
                "lighted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8561312e0c94eb990ce518dfa88eaf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has one ………………………. He is terrified of heights.",
            "description": "A phobia is a compulsive fear of something.",
            "answers": [
                "mania",
                "phobia"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "085ce837748e4f51b49737e277786f8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you do with a partner who has a ……………………….. for watching soccer on television?",
            "description": "A mania is a compulsive love of something.",
            "answers": [
                "phobia",
                "mania"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d35cec205f014045b1b527d5c11235c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is so ……………………… that he constantly changes his political outlooks.",
            "description": "Mercurial means impulsive or erratic.",
            "answers": [
                "volcanic",
                "mercurial"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed0839e947f14464b9a61667bf9a366c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The guests are …………………………. friends of the bride.",
            "description": "Mostly means primarily.",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "mostly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d2409f514884e92a9194c92d5060cfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. everyone enjoyed the party.",
            "description": "Almost is similar to nearly.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Almost"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc63e3954bbf4f05944120011f157229"
        }
    ]
}